All right, so first, the tests come and head off.
We're going to find the task information for the Wi-Fi application free, arduous task.
OK, so who will define details for the Wi-Fi application task?
And we'll define here the wi fi app tests tech sites.
As four thousand ninety six bytes.
Next to find the wi fi app task priority.
And we can make it five.
Next to find the Wi-Fi app task Korede.
As zero.
All right, so that's it, so now we can head over to the wi fi app that see file and we need free auto,
so let's include free autos.
Slash free autos storage.
And will eventually use event groups, so include free autos.
Slash event group stage.
Next include autos.
Task Sturridge will also need to include Espérer Duddridge.
Let's also include the ESP luggage.
And next include the ESP wi fi.
H for wife, driver.
And let's also include.
Lightweight IP slash net DB storage.
And include here, the rugby.
LED.
We also need our tasks underscore a common Derek.
And of course, we need a Wi-Fi uptick.
Next will create a tag used for ESP serial console messages.
And we'll say static const char tag.
And call it wi fi underscore app.
And here, let's create a Q handle.
Used to manipulate the main cue of events here.
And we'll say static to handle.
Underscored T.
And call it wi fi app to handle.
And next, we'll need the network interface objects.
For the station and access point.
And that'll be ESPN that if underscored T pointer to our external ESPN that if they stay variable.
And let's initialize that to now.
We also need our ESP unit if a variable.
Initialized to null as well.
All right, good.
So now let's head over to the wife head of file.
We can grab our prototypes.
Well, let's define them here in the Dead Sea file.
So let's first define a Wi-Fi app, start function, and in this function, we'll handle some initialization
and also define the Wi-Fi app.
Arduous task.
So first, we're going to log a message and we're going to use ESP log info and say tag starting wi
fi application.
OK, so this ESP log information will take our tag and our message string and log it to the serial console.
All right.
So next we'll start our Wi-Fi started.
LED and state rugby led by fire started.
And next, we'll need to disable default by logging messages.
Because we don't want so many messages log to the console, and for that, we'll say ESP log level.
WI fi and the level is ISP log none.
All right, so now we'll create a message queue.
Using our wi fi app to handle.
And use excu create.
To create a queue capable of holding the size of three.
Of Wi-Fi app message structures, so we can just simply grab our Wi-Fi, a message struck.
Place it here.
And then let's start the Wi-Fi application task.
And for that, will use X to create Penta Core.
And he will put a reference to the task function that will create.
Call it wi fi app Teske.
And here at the name WI app task.
Next, will into the wi fi app Stack Size.
And here this is no as we're not passing any parameters.
And now put the wi fi app.
Task priority.
And the next one is no, as we aren't using a task handle.
And here this is our wi fi app, Task Corps.
Right, so now let's head over to the Wi-Fi apps and message function.
So first, we'll create an instance of our wi fi epic message struct.
And call it message, and then we'll set the message, Heidi, to the message I'd passed into the function.
And we're going to return the result of sending to our cue using excuse send.
And we have to specify the handle.
And the reference to the message.
And the time up will be Port Max delay.
So here we're going to pass the message to the function and then send it to the queue specifying our
handle.
And like I said, so far, we're only we only have these messages here available.
Right, so now let's define the main task for the Wi-Fi application.
And the parameters is a point of variable parameter.
Which can be passed to the function.
And here we're going to say static void, why fi app task?
And it's a void pointer PV parameter.
And now this will be our main task for the Wi-Fi application, where we initialize Wi-Fi and receive
all key messages which determines the flow of the application.
So we'll need to define some set of functions which initialize the event handler and the TCP IP stack
in the Wi-Fi config, as well as the soft API config before we start wi fi and send the first message
to the queue.
So I'll lay them all out right here first and then we'll define them one by one.
So let's create an instance of the wi fi up cue message struct and call it message.
Then next, we'll initialize the event handler.
And we'll create a function called wi fi app Event Handler in it.
Also need to initialize the TCP IP stack.
And why fi config and we're going to call it wi fi app default wi fi.
And it.
And the next will do the same for the soft AP config.
And call it wi fi, soft AP config.
And then here we can start by five.
And here, let's SPRO check, so we'll know if the function returns in error.
So call ESP wi fi start now.
Then next, we can send the first event message.
And we'll use a wi fi app, send message.
And since the wi fi start HTP server message.
All right, so now we can create our endless loop.
So come here.
And we're going to say four with two semicolons in parentheses.
And then say, if execute, receive.
And for the first parameter, we need a cue handle.
For the second parameter, we need a reference to the message.
Our message right here, right?
And for the third parameter, it'll be put max delay.
And now will say switch message, that message I.D..
In the first case will be wi fi app Message Start HTTP Server.
OK, great.
And here we can log a message using ESP log information.
With our tag.
And our message, which will be the message genome.
And then we'll create a function called FTP Server Start.
And will define this later, so just comment it out for now.
And then we'll call our IGB led http server started function here.
And then we can include a break.
And then the next case for why fi message?
Connecting from HTP server and then just log a message for this case for now.
And then include the break.
And the next case will be the wi fi app message.
Stay connected, got IP.
Log the message here.
And then we're going to call be led by five connected.
And then we're going to break.
And also, we can leave a default break right here.
OK, next, we can start defining these functions.
But I think now is a good time to take a break.
So let's continue with defining the Wi-Fi app event handler and its function in the next lesson.